

Atlanta, GA

609.892.2662

msjoyjackson@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/joysjackson

www.github.com/joydotcom

Profile

Passionate, Devoted, and Personable Creative with an extensive successful background in Education, Design, and Performance Art. Possessing Leadership, Cultural Competence, and Innovative transferable skill sets. Combining my Software Engineering certificate with uniquely creative professional experiences.

Education

Georgia Tech - Full Stack Web Development Certificate - 2021 William Paterson University - Educational Leadership 18 Graduate Credits - 2018 Montclair State University - B.Sc Kinesiology - 2008

Experience

Web Developer, Georgia Tech Professional Education (Student) – 2021

- Manage teams. Develop & Present Web Applications : Front/Back End Development

<u>Teacher Leader, Ben Hill Private Academy: Atlanta, GA – 2019 - 2020</u>

- Observed & Evaluated Academic and Social Development of Students
- Managed Teaching Staff

Student Development Coordinator/ Teacher: NJ Public Schools - 2009 - 2019

- Implemented, Facilitated & Instructed school-wide (750+) SEAL Curriculum
- Wrote and presented Proposals and Budgets for Community Outreach
- Analyzed, Prepared, and Presented Evidence Data
- Coordinated, Designed, and Choreographed School Productions & Performances

Asst. Manager PT: Nightlife Talent: Atlantic City Casinos & Resorts - 2007 -2015

- Managed Productions and Rehearsals
- 93% Talent Satisfaction Rate

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Node, VS Code, MVC, SQL, Github, Adobe Suite, FrontEnd Design, Team Management, Leadership, Adaptability, Personable, Culturally Conscious, Customer Service, Effective Communication, Attention to Detail, Budget & Proposal Writing, Critical Thinking, Problem Solving, Creativity, Organization, Empathy

Tech Projects

Personal Professional Portfolio - Designer - React.js, Bootstrap, GitHub, VS Code http://www.msjoyjackson.com https://github.com/Joydotcom/react-portfolio

Local Roots - Designer - React.js, Bootstrap, Adobe XD, SQL, VSC: Marketplace for plant lovers.

https://damp-reef-27856.herokuapp.com/ https://github.com/julesscheil/Local-Roots

GamerZ - Designer - JavaScript, CSS, HTML, VS Code : Community for Gamers https://afternoon-garden-82475.herokuapp.com/ | https://github.com/greenkimparsons/gamerz